[Music]
welcome to this session where we talk
about exciting new opportunities for a
partner Community topic today of course
is artificial intelligence and more
specifically generative AI now in March
2023 we introduced you to Dynamics 365
co-pilot the world's first AI powered
assistant across Erp and
CRM uh and in business Central co-pilot
initially had just one skill marketing
text suggestions um giving our customers
that boost of creativity uh by drafting
compelling product descriptions that
help them bring their products to Market
faster now our vision for co-pilot has
really gone well beyond that uh we
always wanted to unlock this new wave of
productivity uh for workers across all
roles across all lines of business
across all Industries and geographies uh
and really help them perform their
day-to-day tasks in a more efficient way
and we couldn't achieve that Vision
without your help our partner
community so we're excited to introduce
new Tools in fact a whole new toolkit uh
for you to give co-pilot and business
Central new skills new capabilities and
include those with your extensions
co-pilot is built on Microsoft's
comprehensive approach to privacy
security compliance and responsible AI
so it was only natural that we' Empower
you as well to build responsibly my name
is Mike borj cardano I'm a product
manager at Microsoft and today by the
end of this session you will be ready to
start implementing your first generative
AI feature uh in Al and in Visual Studio
code now this session is ideal for
developers uh but there's also plenty of
tips for designers product owners uh
even Consultants basically anyone who
wants to understand what are these new
Tools in our toolbox and how do we go
and apply them so with the help of my
colleagues uh I'm going to walk you
through a couple of things um first a
simple example that illustrates how the
developer tools can bring a scenario a
use case to life uh we'll then break it
down we'll focus on two major aspects
two major components of this toolkit um
one delivering a great user experience
but two working with Azure open AI
service we'll share some of the other
benefits you get by building on top of
this platform and finally we'll share
insights into how you can build AI
responsibly to ensure the safety of your
customer and their data so before we
dive in uh let's just take a moment to
understand why we're bringing this set
of developer tools to you our partner
community so first of all uh from a lot
of feedback you've given us we
understand that you need a quick way to
bring your ideas to life right so you
can with least amount of code get that
use case up and running so that you can
play around with your prompt that after
all is the uh the the the challenge with
working with AI which is how do you
engineer your prompts so we're trying to
create a system around that where we
give you all these freebies all these
goodies that help that scenario come
alive and you can focus on prompts build
that proof of concept work and evolve it
really quickly the next thing is you
know we recognize that once our partners
start building generative AI experiences
if you take any given customer they're
going to end up with multiple extensions
from potentially different partners and
each of those are going to have a
different user experience so we thought
how can we Inspire Trust of our
customers here so we're going for
consistency of experience to make sure
that everybody builds in a consistent
way and our customer administrators and
end users have a very familiar and
similar way to work with generative AI
um and as we built our first few
generative AI features ourselves uh we
started to recognize the importance of
building responsibly of applying ethical
AI so we want to share those guard rails
that we have built with you so you have
a great starting point uh but of course
you'd still need to go and invest
further in understanding how can you
build responsibly now all of this
equates to one thing which is that
allows you to bring your product to
Market more quickly so you can compete
in your industry in your local geography
more effectively and after all we do
know that our customers even in the SMB
space are becoming more and more
interested in how generative AI can help
them be more productive let's uh talk
through a couple of details here uh as
well as we enter this so what is this
intended for uh what is the developer
tools intended to address so first of
all this is designed for business
Central online what we often refer to as
SAS uh in terms of AI this is also very
much designed for generative AI uh using
Azure open AI service um the idea is to
assist the human in solving some complex
cognitive task and this is an important
Point assist to human so we're not
building autopilots that automatically
do a whole bunch of things outside of
human control here we're putting humans
in control and that is exactly the
interaction mode that we've built as
well uh this is intended for non-con
conversational experiences what do I
mean by that this means that you know
you're looking at integrating this
functionality into your uh business uh
capabilities uh they have concrete input
and output and a human is there to
review that output before it gets
committed um so this is not a toolkit
for you to build chat Bots and chat-like
experiences
now what's in the box what is in this
toolkit so a couple of different
components uh we'll talk about them in
more detail of course a signature
co-pilot user experience along with an
AI module to help you interact with
Azure open AI service we have plenty of
guides and samples to help you get
started uh but also some common
functions in terms of administration
Telemetry uh and other things to help
you and your customers manage generative
AI when will this be available is is
always the question so let's tackle that
uh you can get Hands-On right now if
you're an Insider using Insider builds
you already have access to the toolkit
today which means you can compile run
and test your generative AI features
offline now uh throughout the wave 2023
release Wave 2 we're going to publish a
minor update that will include toolkit
as well what this means concretely is
that you will now also be able to deploy
test run demo uh your code uh to
business Central online um this also
means you can prepare your app for
appsource and you can also deploy this
to your customers as
well so now we're ready to dive into an
example use case which just illustrates
how you can use the toolkit in a very
simple way think of any project you work
on right you have a project plan it's a
breakdown of tasks uh that are important
to complete that project um and if you
track projects in BC you know that's
called jobs and there's a whole jobs
module built around it but you also know
that how time consuming it is to define
a one-off project plan uh and break that
down there's a lot of data entry there
so this sounds like a great fit for AI
for generative AI in terms of using
large language models understanding of
the world World Knowledge simple problem
solving but also the ability to you
apply creativity and generate a project
plan so let's start out in the jobs list
here and the first thing we're going to
do is use the new action to draft a
project plan a job with
co-pilot and this brings up the dialogue
where I can now interact with co-pilot
and the first thing I'm going to do of
course is enter a few keywords which
explain what the project is all
about there's a simple prompt where I
explain that we'd like to furnish an
office with some particular products in
there and now I'll call upon copilot to
actually generate a project plan a
breakdown of this for a particular job
here you can see you know this beautiful
experience as co-pilot is thinking is
generating and it's already done uh it's
applied that touch of creativity to come
up with a whole bunch of suggested tasks
uh that make up this job uh at the very
top you can see how it's already
pre-filled a couple of different fields
which explain and describe the job as
well so there's a ton of content in here
that's really good for me to get started
but if I'd like to redo that by
adjusting maybe some of the parameters
then I'd go back down to the prompt
again just do make a small edit let's
just switch for example 40 to a
different number to 80 let's change some
of the quantities
here and as I ask co-pilot to regenerate
this
content um those will be taken into
account and a new project plan will be
uh drafted based on
that and there it
is now here of course I can review some
of this content I've got that uh job
structure split into tasks notice how
much information is actually filled in
here and drafted by co-pilot what a
great starting point and once I'm
comfortable with this information I can
choose to discard it or keep it now keep
it tells business Central that I want to
register this in the database I do want
to store this into the database and what
I can do from this point forward of
course is rest upon business Central
Standard functionality to work with jobs
uh to to modify this further and just
take it through the Last Mile and
finalize my job allocating any
additional resources or fine-tuning some
of this information here
so what a great and simple experience
where we illustrate putting generative
AI to work inside business Central now
next we're going to break this down and
we're going to start by looking at the
user experience and for that I'd like to
invite my colleague Cody uh thanks Mike
I'm Cody Hoover an engineer at Microsoft
uh working on this uh new experience
that we'll be showing you today uh so
first let's revisit that experience that
we just walked through uh and how we
started with this action
uh in the command bar uh there's nothing
particularly special about this other
than uh this new image uh property
option that's available to you called
Sparkle this sparkle should be used
across the different co-pilot
experiences that you're building um and
that'll give that consistency for our
users to let them uh understand that
this will be an intelligent co-pilot
powered
experience the action itself doesn't do
anything special it just calls uh a page
uh with page run model and that page
will be where most of the magic
happens so if we Zoom back out as soon
as we invoke that action the user sees
this new prompt dialogue page type that
we've been talking about and that we
just saw where the user is able to type
in in a natural language exactly what it
is that they're looking for and let
co-pilot do the
rest let's take a look at the code that
uh defines this this experience this is
a page defined as any other but I want
to focus on these three properties here
the first is the page type property
where we've added a new prompt dialogue
value with this you get uh all of the
responsible AI um and other uh parts of
the experience that are important for
consistency across the different
co-pilot experiences it's also important
to point out that these are required to
not be extensible we want to make sure
that other partners aren't interfering
with your own experience so that
customers can really trust the output um
that they're getting here also I want to
point out uh that we're using this is
preview equals true property that's new
specific for this page type and I'll let
Mike describe when you might want to use
that and when you're ready to remove it
thanks Cody well we appreciate that
we're all still learning how to apply
generative AI in a business context uh
so we really want to empower you to
start start small and grow from there
and use the uh preview badge on this
dialogue to really communicate to your
customers that you're still in that
stage uh where you can bring your
features to Market faster and then
collect feedback in fact we advise that
most generative AI features do start
their life out as a preview um where you
can learn and grow and then eventually
work towards making that generally
available as well great thanks Mike and
now that we've looked at sort of the p P
itself let's take a a little deeper look
into the content that appears on the
page so for example this input where the
user could type that
information as you would Define uh the
content on a normal page you do that
within a layout area but for the prompt
dialogue we've added a new prompt area
just like a fact box or the role Center
areas but this one is specific to The
Prompt dialogue now here we've chosen to
add just a single field that allows the
user to type in what we would call
unstructured data they're able to write
in natural language that makes sense to
them their goals uh for this
experience you could put anything you
want here such as additional Fields
groups or parts um to provide a more
structured input but in this case uh
this is exactly what we
want once the user has provided that
experience they want to do the actual
generate action they wanted to get the
output so when they invoke that the
platform will call this new uh system
action called generate in a new area
called system actions now this new Al
construct allows the platform to provide
some specific actions to you as an Al
developer um that you can provide some
limited control over so in this case we
control where to put it and this allows
us to do the orchestration between the
different UI uh parts and behaviors that
you've seen um and you still get to
decide how that magic sauce of the
generation
happens so after you've done that the
user invokes the generate and they get
this great uh beautiful progress bar
that will appear um across all of the
prompt dialogues what's great about this
is this doesn't require any work from
you as an Al developer you don't need to
choose when to start and stop your own
progress dialogue we'll do this for you
by default and in fact we even allow
cancellation of this in case the Azure
open AI Services um take longer than the
user expects to generate um and once
again with no work from you however if
you do want to override the text that's
shown here you can use the progress
dialogue apis that you're familiar with
to uh control that text there's nothing
new
there and then when that's completed the
user will see this
output
this is where the normal uh content area
that you would use on most Pages comes
into play and once again this can
contain anything that you might put on a
card or document page and in this case
we've chosen fields and parts this is a
very structured output um but you could
also imagine this being a more
unstructured natural language output as
well um for example as you might see in
our other video about marketing
text one thing I do want to call your
attention to here is up in the header
the caption of the page here has changed
it doesn't say the page caption that
sort of describes what this is but
instead we're using the data caption
expression to show the user's natural
language prompt input here the idea here
being that we want this to look um to
reflect the user's request and be able
to connect that visually with the output
so this is one Tech technique that we
recommend uh to bring that and make that
more natural for the
user and once the user reviews this
output and they're satisfied with it or
not they're going to communicate that
result to you as a developer by clicking
on this keep it or discard it or okay
cancel button like you might see in a
task
dialogue now there's no additional
constructs needed for you to to act on
this you simply use the enquery closed
page trigger that you're used to again
from test dialogues or you can use the
value return from the page. Run model in
this case uh that is all that's
needed now you may decide that keep it
or discard it is not the way that you
want to communicate this uh for your
scenario so back in the system action
area there are additional okay cancel
system actions that allow you to
override those captions now they don't
take triggers because we want to keep
the code for that centralized um without
adding too many ways to accomplish the
same task um so here you purely provide
a caption and a tool tip um and leave
the on query closed page trigger as your
way of choosing to keep or discard
it now the user as we saw before uh may
want to edit the prompt that they've
given before they keep or discard this
output uh by going up to that uh the
corner of the page
and choosing to edit
it and that is again purely handled by
the platform by using this uh prompt
dialog page type and by using the uh The
Prompt and the content areas and the
platform is able to keep this experience
for you in a way that we hope is a lot
more natural than for example navigate
Pages once the user has edited that
text and
regenerated uh again no work needed on
your part uh for this sort of
orchestration and transition between the
parts however uh there are some
additional features that you can use to
take this even to another level and for
that I want to reference uh a feature
from the marketing text uh feature that
you can see another video on um so here
uh once the user has made a description
uh generated a entity text description a
marketing text description
uh they may want to get multiple
versions of this multiple iterations so
there is a way to add a regenerate
button down in the command bar this is
again a new system action called
regenerate that will light up if you add
this to your system action
area now in the examples we've shown you
so far the uh input area has been or
that prompt area has been the set of
facts all of the the main information
needed to drive the output but there are
some additional knobs that you may want
to offer to users that don't influence
the facts that go into the output but
that may change for example the tone or
the format these can be made available
both in that prompt area and in the
content area by using the prompt options
area which is yet which is a new area
added to the prompt dialogue page these
should be option fields and they'll
appear as drop Downs down in the footer
allowing users to tweak uh the
generation process and that might make
sense for your
scenario now after the user has gone
through this made some of these tweaks
done multiple Generations they may feel
that one of the previous versions was uh
better for them so you can also expose
that history to the user allowing them
to Traverse through multiple iterations
by adding a source table to your page
so whereas some pages we'll use a source
table to iterate through records in a
list here we're using the source table
to show different versions of the
generated output and of course it's
important to note that these tables
should be temporary because we want the
user to have to uh confirm that they're
ready to accept the output and we don't
want accidental
commits next there may be scenarios
where you want to get input from a file
rather than forcing the user to type
something uh in which case we have again
another system action called attach
which will make this paperclip icon
appear on the footer here you can use
the file upload apis that you're used to
uh to prompt the user to upload a file
and then you'll be able to use that in
your uh co-pilot generation in a way
that again makes sense for your
scenario and finally you may decide that
you already have the information you
need to jump directly into to generation
in that case you can control how the
page opens in for example the onopen
page trigger by setting the prompt mode
on the page directly to generate when
this is done the page will immediately
call your generate action and uh go
directly to this loading State and then
after the generation is complete it will
show uh the generated
output and that's a just an overview of
the uh prompt dialogue page capability
and now I'll pass it over to Derek to
tell you about the a module that will
allow you to do this co-pilot generation
yourself thanks Cody for showing us how
to build the prompt dialog next up I'll
be showing you how to build uh using the
AI module um all the Nitty Gritty bits
underneath that prompt dialog so what
I'll go through is the overview of the
modu kind of building your experience
with it um and Talking a little bit
about the optional parameters uh that
you can call with the mod the the models
so let's get into it so the overview of
the modu so it supports the aure open AI
service so specifically the llms like
text chat and embeddings so it does not
uh allow image generation using like Del
e or transcribing text um Speech to Text
uh with
whisper um it also allows you to control
and view the C capabilities within your
environment which Mike will talk about
later on uh and also gives you Telemetry
so all this Telemetry allows you to
track a capabilities um usage
registration errors um and what other
details that you actually
need so the module is in the system
application uh and all the objects
within this toit can be found within the
system. a namespace
so coming to the prerequisites of using
this
module um you need your Azure open AI
resource URL um so this is an example of
the uh URL where you replace resource
name with what your resource name is
actually called um then you have a
deployment name which would be which
will symbolize the model uh that you
actually using in this case I have it
called my gbd 3.5 you would have a
different name uh for your
and finally you would have the Azure
open AI uh API key uh and I have a link
at the bottom it's where you can go and
apply to get uh access to the Azure open
AI
service so let's talk a bit about the uh
modes
objects So within this module um these
are some common objects uh specifically
for just co-pilot in general so not
degeneration bits um here we have a um
public code unit and two enums so the
co-prod capability um code unit what it
actually has is functions for you to
register your capability modify or if
you want to get rid of it you can
unregister it as well uh you can also
check if it's been registered and
whether it is uh active or not uh as an
admin could disable the
capability uh within the coil
availability uh enum um the two states
uh whether your capability is in preview
or it's generally
available and finally the other enum is
the co-pilot capability enum and in this
case this is where you have to extend
this enum to put your capability in and
let me explain a little more about
that um so for example here I have
extension a that has um Extended the
enum to add capability one so in this
case now uh extension a registers
capability one uh into the co- co-pilot
uh
capabilities uh and then does its
generation and whatnot this is all
great uh in the case now there is
extension B it doesn't extend the enum
uh and tries to use the capability one
however it doesn't register uh it with
the copile capabilities and in such a
case when extens B actually tries to do
any generation this will fail uh
extension B can use capability one only
if it registers it as
well uh so kind of small recap about
that is that each extension must
register with the co-pilot capability
code unit um for the enum uh otherwise
an error will be thrown that the
capability enum is not used or is not
registered uh with the extensions that
is used
it so let's get into the AI um the Azure
open AI uh objects so these are the
common um objects the edile open AI the
Ile open AI operation response uh and
the model type however we have more than
that um specifically for text
completions it's we have the a open AI
text completion parameters these are
optional parameters that can be modified
for uh generation and and also chat
completions uh where you have the ual
open AI chat messages uh AI chat
completion parameters um similarly for
the text these two are almost the same
except they have different parameters
and the Ed open AI chat roles um one one
might be asking embeddings it is
supported but why is there no object for
it um it is just that there is no um
specific um object for embeddings in
this case of like optional parameters uh
embeddings does not have any optional
parameters so let's get into each of
these uh objects so they AER open AI uh
object uh you can check whether Ed openi
is enabled for your environment uh you
can set the authorization and in this
case you'll be setting the resource URL
the deployment name and API key which
I'll get into F the details later um you
can set the co-pilot capability that
you'll be using with um the
generations and then there are the
generate uh text completion generate
embeddings and generate chat completion
um so you might want to take a note here
where uh text completion and embeddings
do return values so in this case of text
completion it return returns a text and
this is the exact uh output uh that you
would expect um from the
generation however if you were to use
the uh AED open AI operation response as
I would show you here you're also able
to get the result however this result is
actually adjon of what was returned so
that is a minor note you want to keep
note of and for example with the
embeddings um get result here actually
returns you a Json list and not a list
of
decimals so with the operation response
as I mentioned you can get a result you
can check if it's successful a
successful run um if it errored out um
you you might want to check uh what was
the status code of the call um and get
what was the actual error that came
through um and for the enam of the model
type uh we as I mentioned we support
three embeddings Tech completions and
chat
completions so if we now look at the
tech text completion uh completion
parameters um this supports for example
set max tokens uh set temperature set
presence penalty they're also the GS for
these uh methods and there many more um
that you can modify uh for your
generation and we then go towards the
check completions now there's the uh
chat messages object so we have the the
first one being the set primary system
message and this is important to note as
this is where you would want to set your
metod prompt um and we recommend that
you bring your own meta promp uh which
is specific to your
capability uh I'll talk a little more
about that uh in a little bit um you can
set how long the history length uh of
the messages you would like um you can
add additional system messages assistant
messages and user messages the key thing
to note is that when you set a primary
system message it will always be
included in regardless of the length
that you specify so for example if you
specify a length of five um one of those
five will always be the primary system
message and then we will take the last
four messages uh that you add in the
list um similarly for the cheat
completion parameters this is the same
as the text completion uh parameters the
only differen is that it might have more
or less um parameters depending on the
azure openi
service and lastly uh for the chat roles
um there are only three roles right now
um there's the user role the system role
and the assistant the user is basically
the when the end user inputs something
you want to use the add user um for the
system it's you're treating it as a meta
prompt or guiding the system in some way
and the assistant is basically the model
returning you some kind of output
so let's register a capability so I as I
had mentioned first you need to extend
the co-pilot capability and here I've
extended it with draft a job so kind of
following in line with what cod had
shown
us um and you will want to have an
install code unit that will register
this uh capability so I'll dive in uh
specifically to the register capability
function so here it is uh what you want
to do is first check has this capability
been registered with this uh extension
so when you call this capabil uh call
this function uh you only need to put in
the enum that you'll be using and it
will automatically take up what uh
extension is calling it so we'll be able
to then check hey has your extension and
this enum been registered and if it has
not then you'll want to register your C
ability so you put in the capability you
want to register uh what the
availability is in this case I'm making
it generally available and a learn more
URL as this will surface within the
admin page um whenever admin wants to
take a closer look at hey what does this
capability actually
do so let's go on to setting up your
authorization but just before setting it
up um you might want to save this in
some way so as I had mentioned earlier
in the prerequisits these are three keys
that you would have um for using this
module so the resource URL your
deployment name and your API key so how
do you go about saving your
authorization and what do we
recommend um there are two ways of doing
it U one is via isolated storage or
using key VA so if you go down the
isolated storage way um you'll want to
create a page such that you can then key
it in manually and save it into isolated
storage as you do not want to hardcode
any Keys uh Etc in your
extension the other way if you're
building an appsource app is to use the
appsource KEYT that you have um and save
it in there so in this case um for this
uh demo uh we'll be using isolated
storage and here my set authorization uh
is basically going to set the
authorization being used for this
generation so here I'm getting my
endpoint my deployment and my API key
and with that I just need to call aure
open AI set authorization I set the
model type that I will be calling as
let's not forget that uh each deployment
uh is a specific model so not all models
would support say text and chat um M
might uh support only text or all
support only chat um and embedding
models do not support either of those um
so key distinction there and then I I
put in the endpoint deployment and API
key so then we have our authorization
authorization
setup so now let's go into generation so
this is a very brief view of what the
generation code looks like in a
minimalistic form but let's go into what
that code actually is so here's the
generate code um so I had already
mentioned about setting your
authorization um next I want to set some
parameters so I'm since I'm using the
check completion I want set those
parameters and how do I do that and here
I just call the function of set max
token and set temperature so in my case
I want to have I want to use a longer
token range um and because I want to
structure output um I'm setting the
temperature to zero um and those are the
only parameters that I'm
changing and once I've set those uh I
want to set the capability I'll be
calling this with so in this case it's
the capability that I had uh extended
and uh registered so draft the job and
next I want to put in my meta prompt so
here let me talk a little bit about what
meta proms are and what they should
have so metap problem should Define the
model's profile I mean should what it
does and what it cannot do it should
also Define what kind of output You're
Expecting for example in my scenario I'm
expecting it to give me back some XML
which I'll show you in a moment um you
should also provide examples to type
help guide the model to give you back
what you want and also provide
additional uh behavioral guard rails
such that it doesn't go off the rails
and protects um your end user uh which
Mike will talk a little bit about at the
end uh about responsible
AI um so here is an example of a meta
prom for this um uh demo so you are
telling the system that you are an AI
assistant in business Central that helps
the user draft project tasks in the
following XML format so I'm expecting
this XML format with project a
description um some tasks and in this
case there will be a task uh which has
description start date and date and
resource
role um and then at the end I'm telling
it hey if a user asks you a question you
don't know say so now this is only an
example it does not Encompass like
limitations Behavioral safeguards or
examples of intended Behavior which you
should do and you can read more about it
at the Azure open AI Service uh
documentation so now now we go back uh
to the code uh once I've set my meta
prompt now I want to add the actual
prompt that my user has uh written
in and from there I can actually call My
Generation now so as open AI generate
check completion I put in my chat
messages my parameters that I want I
changed and the operation response so
that I can get back whether this was
successful or not and the first thing I
do is check hey was this successful and
my case uh when it is I just want to get
back the result from the last message
and that and it would just be the XML
format um and I can just return that and
do some postprocessing of that XML after
that so now talk a little bit about the
optional
parameters so as I had mentioned it's
only supported for chat and text as
embeddings does not have any um optional
parameters at this time uh it's used
it's used to control the models um so
for example with temperature whether you
want to structured uh output or
non-structured um where structured is
basically zero as I had shown because I
want an XML format uh I can increase the
amount of tokens I want to use so if I
know I want something that's to be short
I I shouldn't use too I shouldn't set my
Max tokens to be short uh such that the
model doesn't end up generating more
than it uh
should uh then there's like presence
penalty and many more U that you can
look at at the documentation however I
also like to mention that not all
parameters are support for example n and
n is basically the number of generations
um that the model should return uh where
if it selected like say n equals 3 um
instead of it just returning one
response it will return three responses
at the same time and let you select it
however this is not support
it and lastly I would just like to
mention if you think our AI module is
missing any features is that this uh
module is on GitHub it's part of the
system application layer um so you'll be
able to go there um ping us uh write a
uh create a pool request and then let's
get that in all right Mike can you tell
us more about the administration page
thanks d so one benefit of registering
your capability with business Central is
that it allows you to plug into this
administrative backbone that business
Central offers to our customers and we
believe that customers should remain in
control of their data and of their AI
experiences so here we have the new
co-pilot and AI capabilities page this
is intended for admins and it serves
really two purposes first is providing
transparency and secondly is providing
control let me walk you through that so
um any features that you've registered
will show up here this page includes
features from Microsoft uh from partner
add-ons from any customizations custom
ptes that have been deployed to this
environment um and we'll also split them
by those that are in preview versus
those that are generally available now
those capabilities also always start off
as active but we've given administrators
control to actually deactivate a feature
of their
choosing um now when they do that we
actually ask for a little bit more
information from that admin hey why are
you actually deactivating this feature
this is information we capture and we
share with you as the partner developer
for this feature as well to understand
why are customers deactivating that
capability so here we're providing
discoverability of your capabilities to
those admins uh but also let's talk
about control next we talked about
deactivating but there's there's
actually more so one of the things that
is super interesting is um how does a
customer govern their data and access to
Azure openi service so if a customer is
in a geography in a region where they
have Azure openi service deployed um
then there is no additional setup that
they need to do to start using co-pilot
how fantastic is that we've eliminated
all of that friction to get started
however there's going to be cases where
as a customer you're in a a region where
you don't have AZ Azure open AI service
so what does the experience look like
there in that case admins will need to
do a one-time optin uh to basically
consent to having business Central
contact that Azure open AI service
outside of their regions so we always
advise that our customer admins they
review privacy they understand the
implications and compliance of this
before making this choice but once they
hit that switch uh essentially now
compil it is ready to operate and all of
the features here are able to uh start
functioning in within that organization
now there's also a number of cases where
uh we have automatically opted in uh
that particular customer but admins can
also opt out from this very same switch
over here now all of these three cases
right you've got Azure openi service
within your region you've got Azure
openi service out of your region where
you must give consent and then this
third case where in some cases we will
Auto opt you in admin can op out those
three cases apply to all of Microsoft's
co-pilot capabilities and to your
capabilities as well so the Assumption
here is that you have deployed um your
models also to the same regions as well
now we're going to continue working on
this over time to figure out how we can
give you more control over the situation
when you want to break free from that
and also have your Azure open AI service
endpoints in different
regions note also here that there is no
master kill switch for co-pilot co-pilot
is now on by default it's available by
default as part of business Central it's
an integral part of business
Central now a lot of that in putting
customers in control is all about
responsible AI so I want to take a few
moments to talk about what this is
Microsoft's been investing in ethical AI
for years actually uh and you know we've
come up with these principles which we
hold very dear to our heart and we think
are very important to reflect also in
the extensions that you build um these
principles include fairness reliability
and safety privacy and security
inclusiveness transparency and
accountability and we believe in these
so much that we've actually shared a lot
of these principles guidelines and uh
material that will help you even assess
your own features against these kind of
principles and all of that material
you'll find at
aka.ms now I do want to dive into two
particular cases here starting with
transparency um there's a lot of things
that the toolkit provides out of the box
for being transparent that there is AI
at work here for example uh the
disclaimer on every single output screen
uh in the prompt dialogue which says AI
generated content may be incorrect right
that disclaimer will always show up
there you don't need to add it
yourselves now why is that really
important well it is because AI can
sometimes be incorrect so especially in
cases where you have a a use case which
is very creative shall we say it has to
produce some text um there are risks
there around that uh containing
fabrication so things that are not real
not true um there are cases where that
for example could even produce harmful
content it could include content that is
um you know offensive potentially so we
do want to make sure that customers
understand that this is AI generated and
that they also should review that
material as Cody showed earlier you know
we've produced the entire prompt
dialogue experience around the fact that
there's some kind of input that uh the
user provides then there's output that
the user reviews and only when they
choose keep it do they actually
committed to the
system that's the AI disclaimer but
there's more things as well that you
should consider as you build your
capabilities for example um definitely
use various signals to imply that this
is AI at work use the new Sparkle action
image on your action that opens up that
co-pilot dialogue uh use words like
draft generate suggest co-pilot all of
these help land that signal that there's
AI at work and finally provide
documentation that gives your customers
that transparency about what's going on
behind the scenes ultimately we need
them to trust this technology that you
have used and utilized in your
extensions um and we need to help them
understand the implications to their
data and as they work with the system
what this
means let's talk about reliability and
safety so uh one of the things that you
get for free shall we say by using this
toolkit is user feedback and user
feedback um through the prompt dialogue
here we have the users have the ability
to like or dislike and even provide a
reason uh for that as well this becomes
something you can monitor in your app
insights elry and in powerbi to make
sure that the quality of output for AI
because AI isn't always correct um that
is something you can monitor and act
upon to improve the quality of your
features along with that uh we know that
our partners also want to have insights
into what is usage like what is adoption
like in different regions so we also
provide you with that Telemetry signal
so you can understand how is your
feature being used and finally um as
Derek explained as well uh when you
design your prompt and you engineer your
prompt you want to think about how can
you build into that additional safety
mechanisms uh that could be meta prompts
um or could also be things like content
filtering especially in those use cases
which are more of a creative case like
creating a job project breakdown there
again so that would be a good case where
you want to apply additional code and
thought process to how can you make that
absolutely safe now this is an area we
know that our partners uh would like
some more assistance with so we're
actively working right now on how can we
provide um additional safeties ourselves
through the toolkit you'll hear about
that more later
on all right so before we close let's
just summarize everything we heard today
uh we've got new developer tools to
build co-pilot capabilities in business
Central they're available already right
now with Insider bills um here we
focused on generative AI specifically
with Azure open AI service um it comes
with a whole bunch of goodies including
that signature co-pilot experience which
we know will deliver that wow experience
to your customers um and this is
designed for business Central
online couple of resources to leave you
with to so you can proceed from here and
start writing your code so first of all
as Derek mentioned make sure you get
your Azure openi key uh go to
aka.ms AI apply uh secondly we've taken
a whole bunch of documentation and
guidelines that I mentioned earlier
you'll find find them at this link here
as well aka. msbc start coding with AI
learn all right if you still have a bit
more time and you're looking for
inspiration uh we've got two co-pilot
capabilities in the box with business
Central so go check out the dedicated
sessions where we Deep dive into each
one marketing text suggestions and bank
account reconciliation
assistance there's of course plenty more
resources if you're looking to engage
with the product team if you're looking
to learn about business Central or
follow that buzz on social media um here
are some links you can use and I also
want to call out this one in particular
which is especially for our partners who
want to get involved with AI join our
Yammer Discussion Group specifically for
co-pilot and Ai and also you know as you
come up with those great ideas if you'd
like to share them with the world share
your screenshots of how you're putting
this toolkit to work uh and
hhms dyn 365 BC um like that you can
share your ideas with the world and we'd
love to see
them so with that I'd like to thank you
for spending time with us we hope that
uh you found this useful that you can
start building your generative AI
experiences we're so looking forward to
hearing your feedback so on behalf of
the team here thank you for your
time